Hello, welcome to the next episode of Learn German in Hindi.
Today,
in global concepts, we are going to
take a small test on all the economic problems.
Many people had asked me in the comments
and I also thought that it would be good for you too.
If you solve this test,
you will know whether your concept is clear
or not and if not, then you
can revise it as constructed. I am
going live next Wednesday, March 24th, at 9:30 pm India time.
If your concept is not clear, then you
can ask me there and
I hope that you will
solve it immediately and then you will get an idea of
how much you have understood. So
let's start with the test. Right now
you will see these 25 questions on the screen.
Solve them without any help for a long time. Now you
can pause it. When you have
solved it completely, remove the
points and you can see the answer.
I hope that all of you will enjoy it.  You must have
solved this question now let's all
see the answer together
first of all very simple I play cricket
spoiler cricket ki is character exit ke dar how I can
drink team dal and isiye is
contest prince kaun imer similarly I will
play cricket is verid cricket club
avyakt ok now questions what do you
play what do you play is just falls into which
month in which you have a word he just do
maturity one position
ki table pe faluda pizza edition abhi
passed by a watch student is wale
student hi and deputy mayor hut love
dv plate cricket viewers paytm cricket
now we will go to present perfect I want to
them ishq bina punj gyan dhan dhan
why place is changing if you remember
then abhi pass perfect ki hai digital
pizza so in German also help hut pizza
questions abhi let's see the cases a little I
play with the ka with what is midnight you
neutral dam isiye is drink
mid-day murder  so I love my father how to do this
play mother would be
good winner that's why it
is minor that's why puck minor daughter fix for his
early on for what is a registrar egg
cockpit what is unit pasta to UNESCO that's why I will
give this pasta I wake up and not
wake up what is that destroy breaks that's why
work those nine and after that whatever place
with me what happens in this mixture that's why
that thing payment rich and after that go
meeting pizza question German will
not continue this effigy of that
many times cricket is plated crickets
plate what will happen in festive season otherwise
cricket British field
that if you are saying time it is 830 then
what will happen and if you want to say money then state of the
word Rajesh or in formal kneading is
east hall nine emotions after this
what happens in 32 AIDS patient whatever happens that's why
test job English B ka tree right now I
can help my friend elephant what is
tumor that's why Ishq un my name for
and help in two is
Arabic and  I conjunctions identity people
like team why did I go for this trick paid by step study
that he is similar if
placed for made that ball ishq love kush
will vanish in the bible next point
why I am final because of one because you
are Jatav how many marks did you get from peace comment that
if possible then write in the comment below
understand where you made mistakes
if the concept is not clear then
revise that episode again and if you want
then you can watch moment means I will come live then you
can ask me for your comments I hope you
liked this episode then see you
in the next episode
K Animal